gistfactory.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Gistfactory

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Gistfactory collects,  
uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each,  
a “User”) of the www.gistfactory.com . This privacy policy applies to  
the Site and all products and services offered by Gistfactory?.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a  
variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our  
site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the  
newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection  
with other activities, services, features or resources we make  
available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, mailing  
address, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site  
anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from  
Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users  
can always refuse to supply personally identification information,  
except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related  
activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users  
whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification  
information may include the browser name, the type of computer and  
technical information about Users means of connection to our Site,  
such as the operating system and the Internet service providers  
utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web  
browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes  
and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set  
their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are  
being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not  
function properly.

How we use collected information

[Gistfactory.com](http://gistfactory.com/) collects and uses Users personal information for the  
following purposes:

– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our  
Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on  
the information and feedback we receive from you.  
– To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your  
customer service requests and support needs.  
– To process transactions  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when  
placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not  
share this information with outside parties except to the extent  
necessary to provide the service.  
– To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we  
think will be of interest to them.  
– To send periodic emails  
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be  
used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order.  
It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other  
requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list,  
they will receive emails that may include company news, updates,  
related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User  
would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include  
detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User  
may contact us via our Site.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices  
and security measures to protect against unauthorized access,  
alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information,  
username, password, transaction information and data stored on our  
Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users  
happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and  
protected with digital signatures.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification  
information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic  
information not linked to any personal identification information  
regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted  
affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use  
third party service providers to help us operate our business and the  
Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out  
newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third  
parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us  
your permission.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to  
the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers,  
sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the  
content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible  
for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In  
addition, these sites or services, including their content and links,  
may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their  
own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and  
interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link  
to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising  
partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to  
recognize your computer each time they send you an online  
advertisement to compile non personal identification information about  
you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad  
networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that  
they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does  
not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART  
cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our  
Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally  
identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information  
about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google  
ad and content network privacy policy at  
<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For  
that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from  
those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is  
structured to attract anyone under 13.

Changes to this privacy policy

Gistfactory has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any  
time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our  
Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you  
an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any  
changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the  
personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is  
your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and  
become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and  
terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not  
use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of  
changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those  
changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of  
this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

info@gistfactory[dot]com
